BHARGAV RAGURU

Chennai, Tamil Nadu

 $\ igsim$ bhargavraguru1990@gmail.com

+91 7075819790

Summary

Service Now a professional with 5 years of hands-on experience in testing ITSM, ITOM, and HRSD modules. I've been working as a Tester, and I have run many types of testing for both Manual and ATF testing. Hands-on activities like Acceptance, Capability, Integration and Regression Testing. Well versed with Agile methodology sand Waterfall method. Motivated, focused and dedicated towards the completion of the task along with strong leadership qualities. Always looks forward to working in a learning environment to improvise work and knowledge.

I'm carrying overall 10 Years of experience in various Domain- Telecom, Minerals & Mining, Food & beverages, Digital Entertainment.

Skills

Technical competency

- Service Now
- Power BI
- Advance Excel
- Power Point

Certifications

- Certified System administrator SNOW
- Service Now Delta certified- Tokyo
- Automated Test Framework (ATF) certified
- Agile Scrum methodology

Work Experience



Navigate your next Infosys Technologies

Designation - Test Analyst Jun 2022 - Present Domain - Telecom

- Experienced in analyzing the business requirements with Client and Development team and responsible for creation of detailed Test plan, Test Case Design and carry out execution.
- Well versed with Test Management tools like JIRA to create/manage Test Scripts, Test Execution, defects logging, monitor their resolution status and defect retest and status report to clients on the Testing progress.
- Conducted functional testing includes Integration Testing, Regression Testing, System Testing, End to End testing, Sanity Testing, Compatibility Testing.
- Worked in an Agile (scrum) methodology and interacted with Client, Developers, Business Analyst, and other team members during all the Sprint ceremonies and involved in reviewing and analyzing product backlog, sprint planning and user story estimation.
- Delivered Test Summary Report Signoff after each Testing phase with detailed test execution details.
- Experienced in handling the testing team of 4 members during multiple releases in each phase like work assignment, tracking progress of team on assigned work and capable to work individually and handle all the testing activities.
- Experienced in automating the Regression Suite using Automated Test Framework(ATF)
- Explicitly involved in Domain Separation and created Data packs.
- Hands-on experience in creation of Reports and presentation with various concepts like Tracker, Closure, Audit, testing cycle, Domain Separation and ITSM modules.



Evalueserve India Pvt Ltd.

Designation – Sr. Business Analyst Oct 2021 – Jan 2022 Domain – Metals and Mining

- Responsible for recommending and testing solutions on the Service Now platform to satisfy business needs. Supporting the business process owners in configuring the platform and customizing Service Now in the execution.
- Worked in Rest API and Postman to execute API integration flow with JSON payload and tested Events, Inbound and Outbound journey.

- Conducted functional testing includes Integration Testing, Regression Testing, System Testing.
- Worked in a Waterfall methodology and interacted with Client, Developers, Business Analyst, and other team members for Test Plan to execute flow of Test Scenarios, and Test Cases.
- Delivered Test Summary Report Signoff after each Testing phase with detailed test execution details.
- Conducted Demo sessions to give overview of implementation to respective Product Owners and Stakeholders.



Designation - Data Analyst Aug 2018 - Oct 2021 Domain - Food and Beverages

- Worked on Data creation in Test, and UAT across ITSM, ITOM Modules.
- Conversion of business requirements into technical requirements
- Hands-on experience UI Policies, Business Rules, Events Rules and Alert management conditions and SLA configurations.
- Expertise in coordinating and working in all phases of the Software Testing Life cycle such as analysis of business requirements, creating test strategy, test planning, identifying scenarios, test data creation, test execution, defect tracking, issue escalation and test results walkthrough.

Project 2: Social Media Listening & Analytics (Data Analytics, Engineer)

- CES Dashboard: Prepared interactive dashboard for CES (Call, Email, Chat & Social care) on TALK Frame using the Power BI
- Industry report (Food & Recipe, Coffee & College Students): Delivered social media BI report where requirement was to get know the trends, Consumption Pattern, Top Theme & Influencers analysis on social space.
- Story building, Visualization & preparing suitable format for the reports
- Responsible to create Ad hoc report requested by the client

$autumn \\ \textit{GREY} \\ \textit{Autumn Advertising India Pvt Ltd.}$

Designation - Data Analyst, Social Media & Insights Analyst Apr 2017 – Aug 2018 Domain – Beverages and Digital Entertainment

- Provide insightful social media listening report with key action items for Stakeholders.
- Leading a team of digital analysts to shape up high quality social media listening report



Designation – Management Trainee Apr 2016 – Dec 2016 Domain – Kitchen Appliances

- Do an industry level analysis that would comprehensively look at trends in the industry under the spotlight
- Setting up the process of real time tracking of new platforms.

Achievements

- Insta-Rise Award in Infosys
- Applause Award in Telecom Project.
- Spot Award in Infosys

Education

- Post Graduate in Master of Business administration 70%
- Graduate in B-Tech EEE 66%

Personal Details

- Marital status Married
- Languages known English, Hindi, Telugu, Kannada, and Tamil